<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Developing Transboundary Conservation Network from Mountains to Deep Seas</title>
    <link>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Developing Transboundary Conservation Network from Mountains to Deep Seas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, DMAD; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/livestream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/livestream/</guid>
      <description>Watch our livestream
x</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>HOW TO PREPARE THE ABSTRACT modified from J. Etterson and L. Shannon The abstract is a brief, clear summary of the information in your presentation. A well-prepared abstract enables the reader to identify the basic content quickly and accurately, to determine its relevance to his/her interests or purpose and then to decide whether they want to listen to the presentation in its entirety. An abstract must be included on your seminar posting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Information</title>
      <link>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/information/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/information/</guid>
      <description>Organisation DMAD We are working on to fill the scientific knowledge gap on cetaceans in the Mediterranean Sea in hand with providing active community involvement to our research and conservation actions for the purpose of Marine Protected Area delineations. Currently, we coordinate three different projects all in successful manners, with solid outcomes in Turkey, Greece and Montenegro. We are aware that without the involvement of stakeholders and decision makers in equal importance with our scientific activities, project outcomes will be only paper based with no real life adapted regulations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you.</title>
      <link>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your submission We will take a look at it and we will notify you shortly.
Home</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>