<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>From Mountains to Deep Seas</title>
    <link>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on From Mountains to Deep Seas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, DMAD; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/livestream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/livestream/</guid>
      <description>Watch our livestream
x</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abstract</title>
      <link>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/abstract/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/abstract/</guid>
      <description>Instructions on Submitting Abstracts Deadline for submission of abstracts: 1 November 2017 (23:00 GMT)
Only one abstract per author can be submitted, in one of three different formats: long-talk, short-talk and scientific poster. Long-talks must be presented by the first author, while short talks and scientific posters can be presented by the co-authors.
Upon submitting you will be asked to attach a document containing the following:
Abstract title: no more than 20 words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Information</title>
      <link>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/information/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/information/</guid>
      <description>Conference mission Effective nature conservation is only possible with transboundary research efforts, particularly if the target animals rely on long migration routes for their survival. There are over 100 projects in the Balkans and Turkey supported by Rufford Small Grants, many of which have the same target species and aims. However, with the differences in their methodology and scope, the potential to reach a common goal and create transboundary conservation measures is diminished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you.</title>
      <link>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your submission. Thank you for your abstract submission to the 27th Rufford Conference in Montenegro. Your abstract will be reviewed by two independent researchers. The approval of your abstract will be emailed to you before December 1st, 2017. If you do not receive an email from us by that date, please notify us.
Looking forward to seeing you in Montenegro!
Kind regards, Dr. Aylin Akkaya Bas</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>