<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>From Mountains to Deep Seas</title>
    <link>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on From Mountains to Deep Seas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, DMAD; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/livestream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/livestream/</guid>
      <description>Watch our livestream
x</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abstract</title>
      <link>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>Instructions on Submitting Abstracts Deadline for submission of abstracts: 1 November 2017 (23:00 GMT)
Only one presentation will be accepted per presenting author First authors must be registered by the late registration deadline (1 December 2017) Short talks and posters can be presented by the co-authors
Abstract title: Provide the title of the abstract, no more than 20 words.
Authors’ names: Provide the authors’ names, surnames and Institutes/affiliations.
Abstract: Abstract should be one continuous paragraph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Information</title>
      <link>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/information/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/information/</guid>
      <description>Conference Objective  Developing a cross boardary online network for data standarisation in the East Adriatic There are several projects conducted in the Adriatic but few have solid ground breaking outcomes Nature conservation is only possible with transboundary protection/conservation/management measures, spesifically if the target animals have a long migration routes. Its already proven that inter connnected cross boardary protected habitats are the strongest step on both species and ecosystem level protection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you.</title>
      <link>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conference.montenegrodolphinproject.org/thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your submission. Thank you for your abstract submission to 27th Rufford Conference in Montenegro. Your abstract will be reviewed by 2 independent researchers. The decision of your abstract will be emailed to you before December 1th, 2017. If you do not receive an email from us by that date, please notify us.
Looking forward to seeing you in Montenegro
Kind regards, Dr. Aylin Akkaya Bas
Back to the homepage</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>